Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive, 1989-2004 MSS.191
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Series I: Red Hot + Blue, 1990; 105140
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 131863
    - Single: "I've Got You Under My Skin," Neneh Cherry; Circa Records, 1990; cuid8356; 160206 (Box 42)
    - Sweatshirts - David Wojnarowicz artwork and text, c.a. 1990; cuid8357; 161404 (Box 30)
    - T-shirt - safe sex is hot sex, [n.d.]; cuid8358; 161292 (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0001)
- Oversize Series II: Red Hot + Dance, 153999
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 154000
    - Press clippings, 1991; cuid8359; 154001 (Box [46])
    - Promotional limited edition four record DJ box set; Epic Records, 1992; cuid8360; 160209 (Box 42)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161020
    - Double A-Side: Crystal Waters / Sabrina Johnston - "Gypsy Woman" / "Peace;" Epic Records, 1992; cuid8361; 160210 (Box 42)
    - Red Hot + Dance double album; Columbia, 1992; cuid8362; 160211 (Box 42)
    - Remixes of "Too Funky," "Too Jazzy" and "Crazyman Dance," George Michael; Columbia, 1992; cuid8363; 160208 (Box 42)
      Sound Disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
    - Single: "The Boy From Ipanema," Crystal Waters; verve Records, 1996; cuid8364; 162321 (Box 42)
      Sound disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
    - T-shirt - Red Hot + Dance, 1993; cuid8365; 151816 (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0002)
    - T-shirts - safe sex is hot sex, male couple, [n.d.]; cuid8366; 161291 (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0003)
    - T-shirts - safe sex is hot sex, male couple close-up, [n.d.]; cuid8367; 161290 (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0004)
- Oversize Series V: Red Hot + Country, 128576
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 128577
    - Helene Silverman (Restricted), 1993 - 1994; cuid8369; 128578 (Box [46])
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 153993
    - Posters - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.]; cuid8370; 154027 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, 1994 - 1995; cuid8371; 153994 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161423
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.]; cuid8372; 161134 (Box 32, Object ID: 191.2.0005)
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Country, 1994; cuid8373; 161135 (Box 32, Object ID: 191.2.0006)
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Country, 1994; cuid8374; 161136 (Box 32, Object ID: 191.2.0007)
- Oversize Series VI: Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool, 153996
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 153997
    - Posters - Red Hot + Cool & Red Hot On Impulse, [n.d.]; cuid8375; 154020 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, 1994; cuid8376; 153998 (Box [46])
    - Promotional sampler featuring "The Rubbers Song" by The Pharcyde and "Proceed II" by The Roots with Roy Ayers; Red Hot Organization, 1994; cuid8377; 160214 (Box 42)
    - Promotional sampler featuring special new mixes by The Roots and Da Beatminerz; Red Hot Organization, 1995; cuid8378; 160416 (Box 43)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material, 160809
    - Photographs: GRP publicity shots / Craftsmen photo, [n.d.]; cuid8379; 161003 (Box [46])
    - Photographs: Color + B&W, [n.d.]; cuid8380; 160810 (Box [46])
    - Photographs: Stolen Moments Color + B&W, [n.d.]; cuid8381; 161002 (Box [46])
    - Oversize Series VII: Red Hot + Bothered, 154023
      - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 154024
        - Posters - Red Hot + Bothered, 1995; cuid8382; 154025 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Subseries D: Merchandise, 160202
        - Red Hot + Bothered EP's with limited edition fanzines, Volume I Number 1; Red Hot Organization, 1995; cuid8383; 160203 (Box 44)
          Sound Disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 10 in.
        - Red Hot + Bothered EP's with limited edition fanzines, Volume I Number 2; Red Hot Organization, 1995; cuid8384; 160204 (Box 44)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161021
    - Red Hot on Impulse double vinyl; GRP Records, 1994; cuid8385; 160421 (Box 43)
    - Single: "Proceed II," The Roots with Roy Ayers; Red Hot Organization, 1995; cuid8386; 160417 (Box 43)
    - Stolen Moments: Red Hot & Cool double vinyl; GRP Records, 1994; cuid8387; 160418 (Box 43)
      Sound Disc, Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
- Oversize Series VII: Red Hot + Bothered, [n.d.]; 184469
  - Subseries B: Promotional Materials, 184476
    - Posters- Red Hot + Bothered, 1995; cuid8388; 184477 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Oversize Series VIII: The Beat Experience / Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip, 161024
  - Subseries B: Promotional Materials, 181966
    - Poster - Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip, cuid8389; 181967 (Box [45], Folder [14])
    - Poster- The Beat Experience, [n.d]; cuid8390; 184450 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161025
    - Offbeat: The Red Hot Remixes; Red Hot Organization, 1996; cuid8391; 160215 (Box 42)
    - T-Shirt: Offbeat, [n.d.]; cuid8392; 153851 (Box 33, Object ID: 191.2.0008)
- Oversize Series IX: America Is Dying Slowly, 154002
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 154003
    - In-store play sampler; EastWest Records America, 1996; cuid8393; 160419 (Box 43)
    - Posters - America Is Dying Slowly, 1996; cuid8394; 154022 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, 1995 - 1996; cuid8395; 154004
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161026
    - America Is Dying Slowly vinyl sleeve, 1996; cuid8396; 160420 (Box 43)
    - T-shirts - America Is Dying Slowly, [n.d.]; cuid8397; 151814 (Box 33, Object ID: 191.2.0009)
- Oversize Series X: Red Hot + Rio, 154006
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 154007
    - Press clippings, 1996; cuid8398; 154008 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161424
    - T-shirt - Red Hot + Rio, [n.d.]; cuid8399; 161091 (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0010)
- Oversize Series XI: Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin, 154012
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 162317
    - Invoice: Scarlett Letters, 1997; cuid8400; 162318 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 154013
    - Press clippings, 1997; cuid8401; 154014 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161425
    - T-shirt - Silencio=Muerte, [n.d.]; cuid8402; 161109 (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0011)
- Oversize Series XII: Every Nation (from "Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute"), 154009
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 154010
    - Press clippings, 1997 - 1998; cuid8403; 154011 (Box [46])
- Oversize Series XIII: Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon, 1998 - 1999; 105144
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 1998 - 1999; 105145
    - Posters - Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon, cuid8404; 154026 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Press reviews, 1998 - 1999; cuid8405; 105146 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161426
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Lisbon, [n.d.]; cuid8406; 161239 (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0012)
- Oversize Series XIV: Red Hot + Rhapsody, 153989
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 153990
    - Poster sign - Red Hot + Rhapsody, [n.d.]; cuid8407; 161087 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, 1998; cuid8408; 153991 (Box [46])
    - Promotional sampler: Selections from Red Hot + Rhapsody, in collaboration with Levi's; Antilles Records, 1998; cuid8409; 160422 (Box 43)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 160423
    - Red Hot + Rhapsody double vinyl; Verve Records, 1998; cuid8410; 160424 (Box 43)
- Oversize Series XVI: Red Hot + Indigo, 153986
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 153987
    - Press clippings, 2001; cuid8411; 153988 (Box [46])
- Oversize Series XVIII: Red Hot + Riot, 154017
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 154018
    - Posters - Red Hot + Riot, 2002; cuid8412; 154019 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Sampler featuring "Gentlemen," "Shakara/Lady" and "Zombie [Part One];" MCA Records, 2002; cuid8413; 160425 (Box 43)
    - Sampler featuring "Water No Get Enemy," "Fela Mentality" and "Shuffering + Shmiling;" MCA Records, 2002; cuid8414; 160426 (Box 43)
- Oversize Series XIX: General Red Hot Organization, 192060
  - Subseries A: Administration Files, 192061
    - Invoice: CD&L, 2000-01; cuid8415; 192062 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Subseries B: Promotional Materials, 192063
      - Posters - General, 1997-98; cuid8416; 192064 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Press Clippings - General, 1993-98; cuid8417; 192065 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Press Clippings - 10th Anniversary - Art Forum, 2000; cuid8418; 192066 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Oversize Series XIX: General Red Hot Organization, 153979
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 162319
    - Invoices: CD&L, 2000-2001; cuid8419; 162320 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 153980
    - Posters, 1997-1998; cuid8420; 153995 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings: General, 1993-1998; cuid8421; 153985 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Press clippings: 10th anniversary - ArtForum, November 2000; cuid8422; 154005 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 160212
    - "One," U2: AIDS research benefit album featuring photograph by David Wojnarowicz on cover; Island Records, 1992; cuid8423; 160213 (Box 42)
    - T-shirt - "everybody", [n.d.]; cuid8424; 161405 (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0013)
    - T-shirts - Red Hot Organization contributers, c.a. 1994; cuid8425; 161406 (Box 35, Object ID: 191.2.0014)
    - T-shirt - safer sex is hot sex, female couple, [n.d.]; cuid8426; 161295 (Box 35, Object ID: 191.2.0015)
    - T-shirt - safer sex is hot sex, male couple, [n.d.]; cuid8427; 161294 (Box 35, Object ID: 191.2.0016)
- Series XXIV: Organizational Digital Data Storage, 264362
  - All of No Alt, 1996; cuid8620; 264363; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0001)
    This item has been separated from Series IIIA, Box 4, Folder 13.
  - Red Hot + Country Disk, 1994; cuid8621; 264367; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0002)
    This item has been separated from Series VA, Box 5, Folder 76.
  - Red Hot + Bothered #2 Archive, 1992-1995; cuid8622; 264372; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0003)
    This item has been separated from Series VIIA, Box 8, folder 53.
  - Red Hot + Beat, 1995; cuid8623; 264374; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0004)
    This item has been separated from Series VIIIA, Box 9, folder 36.
  - America @ (RHO #7), 1994-1996; cuid8624; 264403; SyQuest 45 MB Removable Hard Disk (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0005)
    This item has been separated from Series IXA, Box 10, folder 27.
  - Elektra, 1994-1996; cuid8625; 264405; SyQuest 45 MB Removable Hard Disk (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0006)
    This item has been separated from Series IXA, Box 11, folder 12.
  - Red Hot # 18, 1993-1996; cuid8626; 264406; SyQuest 45 MB Removable Hard Disk (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0007)
    This item has been separated from Series IXA, Box 11, folder 35.
  - Return to Helene Silverman / Final "America is Dying Slowly" Artwork, 1994-1996; cuid8627; 264407; SyQuest 45 MB Removable Hard Disk (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0008)
    This item has been separated from Series IXA, Box 11, folder 36.
  - Red Hot 16, 1993-1996; cuid8628; 264408; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0009)
    This item has been separated from Series XA, Box 12, folder 47.
  - From Movieplay, Undated; cuid8629; 264411; SyQuest 200 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0010)
    This item has been separated from Series XIXA, Box 23, folder 24.
  - Red Hot + Bothered - Important Beat Stills, 1994-1995; cuid8630; 264412; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0011)
    This item has been separated from Series XIXA, Box 28, folder 9.
  - Red Hot # 15, 1990-1996; cuid8631; 264413; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0012)
    This item has been separated from Series XIXA, Box 28, folder 10.
  - Red Hot Disk 1, 1989-1996; cuid8632; 264414; SyQuest 44 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0013)
    This item has been separated from Series XIXA, Box 28, folder 12.
  - Red Hot Minis, 1990-1996; cuid8633; 264415; SyQuest 44 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0014)
    This item has been separated from Series XIXA, Box 28, folder 13.